divvyhomes.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | Divvy

_Last Updated on November 11th, 2013_

## Scope

We at Plaid Inc. ("we", "us" or "our") know you care about how your personal information is used and shared - and we take your privacy seriously. This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"), and certain non-personally identifiable information, that we gather when you use or otherwise engage (via mobile application, web browsing or otherwise) with our website or services (collectively, the "Service"). It describes what types of information we collect, how we use that information, and who we share that information with.

By using or accessing the Service in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept and agree to the terms, practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we may collect, use, and share your information as set forth below.

This policy does not apply to any website, product or service of any third-party company even if the website or application links to (or from) the Service. Plaid does not operate those websites, products, or services - please always review the privacy practices of a company before deciding whether to provide any information to them.

## Information We Collect

In general, we collect information in a number of ways, including (i) when a client or end-user provides it directly to us via the Website and/or Service, (ii) when we obtain end-user information through trusted third parties including financial institutions, (iii) through your continued access of the Service, including data passively collected through technology such as "cookies". The types of information we collect and our use of that information will depend on whether you are a Website Visitor, Client, or End-User.

By signing up for the Service, whether directly on our site, with one of the third-party applications that uses our software, or by any other means, you consent to these terms. Some features of the Service allow you to provide content, including financial credentials and information, to the Service. All content submitted by you to the Service or collected on your behalf from a third-party (e.g., client) application or a financial institution (e.g., a bank) may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in this Privacy Policy

### Cookies and IP Addresses

We automatically receive and record information from your web browser when you interact with the Service, including your IP address and cookie information. This information is used for fighting spam/malware and also to facilitate collection of data concerning your interaction with the Service (e.g., what links you have clicked on). Generally, the Service automatically collect usage information, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site. We may use this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, but not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us and third parties authorized by us to figure out how often individuals use parts of the Service so that we can analyze and improve them. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer service.

Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Service through the Internet. Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Service and may associate that information with your Account if you have one. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you to take advantage the most attractive features of the Service. This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, third party websites to which a link points may set cookies on your computer.

### Website Visitors

To simply browse our Website, you are not required to provide any Personal Information. However, we may gather non-personally-identifiable information, as described directly above, just for the purposes of monitoring and improving our Website and the Service. We will not share this information with third parties except as a necessary part of providing our Website and the Service, nor will we use it to target any advertisements to you. Of course, if you sign up with or use any of our services, more information is shared.

### Clients

When you use Plaid services as a client, whether paid or unpaid, we will gather and store your name, company name, email address, phone number, billing address, and any other relevant information that you provide directly to us. Any and all test and/or live users that sign up as an end-user of your services fall under the end-user category. If you sign up for a paid account, we will also store the relevant data required to complete your transaction, including but not limited to your financial information, bank account numbers, routing numbers, billing address and company name. We may also rely on a third-party payment processor to complete transactions, and all data shared with them falls under their own privacy policies. Further, we will collect and associate all relevant end-user data with your client account, including but limited to end-user names, email addresses, billing addresses and financial information. We may additionally collect information on the IP addresses, devices, and locations used to access Plaid, which may be linked to your account for fraud detection and prevention purposes. Finally, we may collect additional data for identity verification on an as-needed based determined at our own sole discretion.

### End-Users

As an end-user of any application that utilizes the Service, whether via a client or other third-party, directly via use of our API or other services, or through an application built by us directly, you are agreeing to share financial information with us including, but not limited to, your account credentials, transactional histories, account numbers, and balances/limits as well as general identity data including names and addresses of all account holders. You are enabling us to interact with and through your financial institutions on your behalf and with your consent. We may also retrieve information pertaining to usage of our client applications and other general activity that comes through use of the Service.

We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Service ("Aggregate Information"). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.

## How We Use Personal Information

Plaid uses your Personal Information as follows:

  * To operate and maintain the Service (such as, overall operating and maintenance, providing customer service, fixing malfunctions, testing our security systems, etc.).
  * To provide you with the features, functions and benefits of the Service (such as, displaying to information regarding your financial accounts).
  * To enhance, improve, add to and further develop the Service (such as, creating new features or functions, refining or personalizing the user experience, increasing Service technical performance, etc.).
  * We will use your contact information (such as, your email address or phone number) to provide you with Service notifications.
  * To help personalize the Service experience for you (such as, remembering your information so you will not have to enter it each time you use the Service or providing you with offers, advertisements or features you may like).
  * And for the other purposes referenced in the "Sharing and Disclosure" section below (such as, for the purposes of legal compliance).

_Last Updated on October 2, 2017_

This Privacy Policy describes how Divvy Homes, Inc., doing business as Divvy and Divvy Homes, and its related companies ("we," "us," and "our") collect, use, and share your information when you visit our website located at [www.divvyhomes.com](http://www.divvyhomes.com/) and any of our other websites (our "Websites"), use our mobile applications, if any, (our "Apps"), interact with our application program interfaces and other services we make to interact with you through social networks (such social networks, "Social Networks"; our services that interact with Social Networks, "Social Network Services"), or use other services (our Websites, Apps, Social Network Services and related services are collectively our "Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites or applications that we do not operate or other websites that have their own privacy policies, including Social Networks. By using any of our Services, you are consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## How We Collect Your Information

We use the term "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy to mean any information that can be used to personally identify you, including anonymous information that can be used to personally identify you when used in connection with other information.

We collect Personal Information from you directly through our Services (for example, when you create an account on our Websites or Apps) and by communicating directly with you by telephone and by email. Personal Information that we may collect from you directly includes the following: your name, mailing address, billing address, phone number, username, password, and demographic information.

Through our Services we may request your permission to collect certain information from you on your mobile device (for example, your photographs, information about your contacts in an address book application, or your list of personal connections on a Social Network). If you give us permission to do so, we may share your Personal Information collected in this manner (subject to this Privacy Policy) and send communications to your contacts or Social Network connections about our Services and products available through our Services.

We automatically track and collect the Personal Information about you and your device(s), including your browser type, your operating system, your IP address and device identifiers, your browsing behavior, websites that you visit before or after our Websites, and other technical data about you and your device(s).

We use "cookies" and other data collection tools to gather Personal Information and customize our Services to you. Cookies are small files stored on your device by a web server. We may use both session cookies (that expire when you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (that stay on your device until you delete them). Our Services may use cookies from third-parties (including third-party advertisers) that are placed on your device when you use our Services. These third-parties may collect Personal Information through the use of cookies and other data collection tools to track your activity on the internet over time and across third-party websites when you use our Services.

Finally, we may collect Personal Information about you from third parties and comingle that information with information we collect in other ways. In particular, we may collect Personal Information about you when you use Social Networks (for example, by posting to your feed), when you log into our Website, App, or Social Network Services using your credentials from Social Networks or other third-party websites or applications (for example, when you authorize Facebook to log in and create an account for you on our Website, Apps, or other Services), and when you use our Social Network Services (for example, when you communicate with us through Social Networks to purchase products). We may also collect Personal Information about you from third-party service providers such as payment processors and other businesses that we partner with to offer our Services or sell products through the Services.

## How We Use Your Information

We use your Personal Information to provide, operate, maintain, and improve our Services and products we offer (including conducting market research). We use your Personal Information to communicate with you about our Services and products, about our company, and about your account generally. We may use your Personal Information to send you promotional material from some of our partners. We may use your Personal Information to provide you customer service. We use your Personal Information to improve the security of our Services and to anticipate and respond to unauthorized, fraudulent, or unlawful activity. We may use your Personal Information to personalize the Services to you, including in communications to you through our Social Network Services and in advertising through our Services and through third-party services (including advertising on other websites that we do not operate). If you give us permission on your mobile device, we may send you promotional and non-promotional "push" notifications to your mobile devices about our Services and products available on our Services.

## How We Share Your Information

We may share your Personal Information with third-party vendors, consultants and service providers that work with us in administering and providing the Services and/or selling products. We may share your Personal Information with our employees, independent contractors, and any parent, subsidiary, or affiliated business entity. We may share aggregated information and reasonably non-identifying information with third-parties for advertising, industry research and analysis, demographic profiling, and other similar purposes. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties to deliver relevant advertising and promotional offers to you. This includes advertising that are served by third-parties to you on our behalf on other websites. Although we may use third-parties to serve advertising to you (including, for example, personalized advertising served to you through Facebook), we do not control or review the technologies that those third-parties may use on their websites (for example, cookies) to track and collect Personal Information about you. We may also share your Personal Information with your consent.

If you interact with our Social Network Services (for example, by "liking" products available through our Services), certain Public Information, such as your image, name, and other information you choose to provide, may be displayed publicly and/or to your personal connections on Social Networks (for example, by posting to your feed or your connections’ feeds). Most Social Networks allow you to control what, if any, of your Personal Information is shared on those Social Networks based on your interactions with services like our Social Network Services. Please review the privacy policies and customizable settings of the Social Networks you belong to in order to learn more about controlling how your information is shared on those Social Networks.

If we become subject to a bankruptcy or insolvency proceeding or if we are acquired in connection with a merger, acquisition, of asset sale, your Personal Information may be disclosed of transferred to the third-party acquiring us.

When permitted or required by law, we may disclose your Personal Information to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (1) to respond to claims and legal proceedings (including subpoenas and court orders); (2) to protect our property, rights, and safety; (3) to protect the property, rights, and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (4) to stop any activity that we believe is illegal, unethical, or legally actionable.

## Security

We take reasonable measures to protect the information that we collect from or about you (including your Personal Information) from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, no method of transmitting information over the internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of any information.

## Do Not Track Signals

Many web browsers and devices allow you to transmit "do not track" signals that express your preference not to be tracked across different websites and over time. We currently do not take action in response to "do not track" signals or other similar mechanisms.

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, we will provide you upon your request a list of your Personal Information that has been shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year and the identity of those third parties. To make such a request, contact us at the email address or postal address below in the Contact section.

## Our Policy Toward Children

While we do collect information about the children of our adult customers, our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information as soon as possible.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated version on this website and update the "Last Updated" date above.

## Terms of Use

Your use of our Services is also subject to our Terms of Use which are available at <https://www.divvyhomes.com/terms>, which control if there is any inconsistency between this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

## Contact

To contact us about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [admin@divvyhomes.com](mailto:admin@divvyhomes.com) or send us your information at:

Divvy Homes, Inc.

633 Folsom Street, 7th Floor

San Francisco, CA 94107
